{
    "id": "cb0939fc76cd44d38fd51ee5d164713e",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "One must learn to adapt oneself …………………. new circumstances.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2e82ae72cb7a4f0c802cc23b296096ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must adhere ………………….. the truth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c4eba66681264e6ca0959b21168d284d"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have to finish the work within the time I have allotted ………………….. you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "77a959a46d5243868c52c008c8441cfc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am grateful ………………… your help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3443c5f9ed664f3280f8796a2e2d2221"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am sorry ………………… my inability to accept your invitation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d9c24698ea9544978250fd94b735eef1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The conversation reverted ………………… . the original topic.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "362dc5bcf476441a888c01f4849850e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He succumbed ………………….. his injuries.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "43d009a8a1684b54b3a0419324e6a359"
        },
        {
            "question": "The soldier yielded ………………… the enemy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "71d6842ada604793b1bae74209ca2d57"
        },
        {
            "question": "This style of writing is characteristic …………………. Dickens.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4811c24f47ce4f04b9991eba4bea763f"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must always be cautious ………………….. giving offence.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "072762bc3f944fd098345f2dd37a60cd"
        }
    ]
}